Guide to the Pete Hamill Papers BCMS.0081
Brooklyn Collection
- Series 3: Writing
  - Sub-series 3.2: Books and Articles
    - Notebook*, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - A Time It Was: Bobby Kennedy in the Sixties, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Storyboards*, circa 2000 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - *Piece Work: Cover, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Diego, 1999-2002 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Diego: 1999 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Diego: Cradle Rocks, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Diego: Launch, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Diego: Promotion, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Diego: Reviews, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Diego: SKED, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - *Sinatra: Research, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Sinatra: Draft, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Sinatra: Draft, 6/15/1998 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Sinatra: Backpage, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Sinatra: Clippings, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Sinatra: Discarded Chapters, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Sinatra: Edits, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Sinatra: First Draft, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Sinatra: Galleys, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Sinatra: Notes, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Sinatra: Philips, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Sinatra: Tina and Nancy, 1996-1998 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Sinatra: Reviews, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Sub-series 3.3: Writing by Others
    - Angela's Ashes: Correspondence*, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Angela's Ashes: Manuscript*, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
    - Daily News Dialogue, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Daily News and New York Post, circa 1997, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Daily News Memorial*, 2020 (Box 16, Folder 12)